{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","address":"1 Washington Blvd","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Centerplate","licenseNumber":"066479","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/30/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E610000058856CD726C354C058DBCA6ECD294540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44960","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","inspectionDate":"2019-01-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"3","pfcount":"2","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"5","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"5","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44960","inspectionDate":"1/17/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"package","problemDescription":"Improperly date marked","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Rack(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"44960","inspectionDate":"1/17/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"44960","inspectionDate":"1/17/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Rack(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"44960","inspectionDate":"1/17/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"44960","inspectionDate":"1/17/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"At the Condenser","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"inspectionid":"44960","inspectionDate":"1/17/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dishonestly presented","subProblem":"","location":"SELF-SERVE STATION","subLocation":"In the Display","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"44960","inspectionDate":"1/17/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"sanitizer","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]},{"inspectionid":"41311","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","inspectionDate":"2018-01-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41311","inspectionDate":"1/23/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Cabinet(s) (lower)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"41311","inspectionDate":"1/23/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink back","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-01-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"37644","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","inspectionDate":"2017-01-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"83","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37644","inspectionDate":"1/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \r\n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \r\n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \r\n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"inspectionid":"37644","inspectionDate":"1/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"37644","inspectionDate":"1/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4049","name":"Cobo Hall-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-01-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4049"}}